Let's go
Don't just take your clothes off! You're quite a moron, aren't you?
I've lost my drive, thanks to you. Good night then
Girls shouldn't be smoking
Your skirt is too short
You're on your period? Your mouth would be fine then!
I'm not your doll you know!
You look better in these
Why don't you stay here tonight?
Then get on top of me!
just shut up already!
Don't just take your clothes off, do it more sexily!
Can I put my fingers in from behind? Then let me lick you!
You're reading too much of those magazines, you moron!
Hey, when are you going to be squirting?
...Shut up! SHUT UP!
Just shut up and lie down naked
You're actually quite handsome if you don't open your mouth, you know?
So do you really get why I'm angry?
...why would you actually shut your mouth at this moment? Good night then.
Could you lend me those underwear that you were just wearing?
Could I touch your body? Lower parts in specific?
I can't take it anymore. Let's go to a hotel
...It's not that I'm feeling hesistant
Stay with me as long as tomorrow continues
I love you
Thanks for always being there for me
I just want those typical lines from you.
It's the good part right now, so can you leave that until later?
Don't worry, you look good in anything
It's almost as if your computer is your lover, huh?
When are you going to turn this way? hey?
Look at me!!
If you continue to be like that, I'm going to hate you for real, you know?
I'm not a girl who could be smiling though everything.
There you go again. Are you really listening to me?
Don't just embrace me without a word...!
The time we had a fight over our different opinions of a boring movie...
When a drama's love scene made an awkward atmosphere
And the time my heart throbbed when our eyes met, before we started dating
You always embraced me without a word
I always, always end up forgiving you since I love you after all,
but I also want some kind words from you once in a while.
What exactly is that mouth of yours there for?
To kiss you?
...shut up! Shut up! Shut up! SHUT UP!
Just shut up and lie down naked
You don't have to say anything; I'm going to satisfy you
I wonder myself why I had to fall for such a hopeless guy...?
And you embrace me again without a word, oh my heartbeat!